Find the B in Find Tuning, Refining a Junket, Find Tuning the Shire.
In the file, Refining a Junket, or in the 2D or 3D window that you drag and drop it into,
in the 2D tool bar, select Adjust Boarding Tools.
Empty Select Boarding Tools.
In the property editor, reduce the particle diameter of the board to 10.
Press the Return key to confirm.
Activate Simulation.
Turn off Simulation after Simulation is completed.
Adjust the Junket to make it fit the model.
Use the Position Tool to tilt the board forward.
If you tilt all the boards forward,
the Shire may hang on the arm of the virtual model,
instead of wrapped around the virtual model.
To avoid this situation,
just select the Junket and use the Position Tool to tilt the board forward.
In the 3D window, turn the view to the left view or the right view.
If you want to change it to the left view, press 6.
If you want to change it to the right view, press 4.
Use the Position Tool to adjust the board.
Tilt the board forward a little.
Be careful not to move the Junket away from the model.
Activate Simulation.
Turn off Simulation after Simulation is completed.
To fine-tune some details of the Junket,
select the Move Tool in the 3D tool bar.
Gently pull the costume in the form of a simulation.
Adjust it to make the costume fit the model.
Turn the wantingSide of the mold inside out.
Put the Junket back to its original position.
Use the Plot Tool to fix the Junket.
Click the register button to save the 24 hours.
Press the left Relax button to move the Junket.
Then pull the Junket.
You just have arrived to the W Angle.
Continue.
穿在模特身上
When the costume is adjusted, delete all the pins, press Ctrl and W on the keyboard to delete all the pins
In the 3D window, rotate the virtual model to confirm the jacket, and wear it together on the virtual model
In the 3D window, let's set the size of the team
Then, the model is cut
Free style
Click on the model, select the model, and press Ctrl and W to cancel the creation
Click the model and press Ctrl and W to Dog
The model is ready to be changed that you want in the visual environment
Click the model and press Ctrl and W to clear the selection
Click the model and press Ctrl and W to yes, the model is ready to use in the visual environment